太好了  再见
Okay, great. Bye.
你猜谁要来吃感恩节晚餐
Guess who's coming to Thanksgiving dinner?
西德尼·波特
Sidney Poitier?
我怀念瑞秋
l miss Rachel.
是我爸妈啦
No, my parents.
太好了  我搬进来之后  他们还没来过
Oh! That's great, they haven't seen the place since l moved in.
对  要是你能不提同居的事
Yeah, you know if you could not mention that we live together,
就太好了
that'd be great.
我打算四点左右开动
l was thinking we'd eat around 4.
为什么不能提同居的事
Why can't l tell them we live together?
因为他们不知道我们在交往
They don't know we're dating.
要不要在厨房吃呢
Do you think we should eat in the kitchen?
你为什么没有告诉他们
Why haven't you told them?
我本来要说  真的
Well, l was going to. l really was.
但是后来不知怎的就没说了
But then somewhere, just out of nowhere, l didn't.
为什么没说  他们知道会不开心吗
Why haven't you told them?! Wouldn't they be happy?!
四点左右厨房开饭  到时候见
So, dinner in the kitchen around 4. l'll see you then.
他们为什么不会开心
Why wouldn't they be happy?
因为
Well, because...
主要是
...mainly...
他们不喜欢你
...they don't like you.
-对不起  -什么  为什么
- l'm sorry. - What? Why? Why?
也许是因为你以前孤僻又嘴毒
Maybe because you used to be aloof...or that you're sarcastic
还老爱开玩笑
Or that, y'know, you joke around all the time.
也可能是因为你脱了衣服都乱丢
...or that you throw your clothes on the couch.
这是他们对我的看法  还是你的看法
ls this why they don't like me or why you don't like me?
我知道我应该告诉他们
l know l should have told them.
我不该在意他们的想法
l shouldn't care what they think.
对不起
l'm sorry.
没关系  这没关系
You know, it'll be okay. It'll be okay.
等他们来了  我会表现得很迷人
Because when they come over, I will be all charming,
我会让他们爱上我  然后我们再告诉他们
l will make them love me, then we'll tell them.
你真的觉得这样可行吗
You really think that'll work?
我也可以很有魅力  我不就赢得了你的心吗
l can be pretty charming, babe. l won you over, didn't l?
你应该不能把他们灌到那么醉
l don't think you'll ever get my parents that drunk.
太好了  罗斯
Hey. Oh, good, Ross.
你爸妈喜欢我  对吧
Your parents like me, right?
他们当然喜欢你
Yes, of course they like you.
莫妮卡刚说他们不喜欢我
Well Monica just told me that they don't.
对  他们不喜欢你
Yeah, they don't like you.
你知道原因吗
Do you know why?
也许是因为你很尖酸刻薄
Maybe it's because you're sarcastic
或者是因为
or maybe it's because you--
他们不知道就不要乱猜
lf people don't know, they shouldn't just guess!
太好了  又一个不值得感恩的感恩节
This is great, another Thanksgiving with nothing to give thanks for.
如果你闭嘴的话  我会感恩
Maybe l give thanks for you shutting up, huh?
如果你把我的电动还我  我也会感恩
Maybe l give thanks by taking my PlayStation to my place.
我也爱你
Maybe l love you.
你们好
Hey, guys.
不要  我不想打电动  乔伊
No, l don't want to play video games, Joey!
你们要去钱德勒家过感恩节吗
Are you guys going to Chandler's for Thanksgiving?
对啊  怎么了
Yeah! Yeah, why? What's up?
我和几个舞者朋友想去市里过感恩节
Well. Me and my friends are doing Thanksgiving uptown.
你们有兴趣一起来吗
I thought you guys might like to come.
真的吗
For real?
算了  你们还是去钱德勒家吧
No, but you should go to Chandler's.
我们没有人会做菜
Because none of us knows how to cook,
最后估计都是在喝酒
we'll probably just end up drinking all day.
好  我们去
Ye-ye, we go to yours!
对  我们得过去露个面
Yeah, see, we-we-we have to stop across the hall
毕竟她是我妹妹
because it's my sister.
不过有个妹妹是好事
But, you know, actually, growing up with a sister was nice...
让我很了解女人心
because it really helped me understand women.
你应该告诉你的朋友们
Yeah, you should tell your friends that.
好
Okay.
真不知你怎么能骗到三个老婆
How you got three women to marry you, l'll never know.
菲比  你看  感恩节甜点
Pheebs, check it out! For my dessert...
我选做了一道传统英式酒果酱松糕
I have chosen to make a traditional English trifle!
听起来好棒哦
Wow. That sounds great!
莫妮卡  你呢
And what are you making, Monica?
万一瑞秋的甜点  好吃到被我吃光光
ln case Rachel's dessert is so good that l eat all of it...
别人会没得吃
...and there's none left for anybody else!
我不做
Nothing.
你不做吗
Nothing?
对  我信任你
No, sweetie. l trust you.
所以要是我搞砸  就没有甜点了  是吗
So, if-if I mess this up, there's nothing else for dessert?
你不会搞砸的
You won't mess it up.
莫妮卡  我好高兴
Wow, Monica, I love that.
你真的对我有信心  谢谢
You really have faith in me. Thank you.
技术问题  这些奶油什么时候好
Technical question, how do you know when uh, the butter's done?
它变成那样子的两分钟前就好了
lt's done about two minutes before it looks like that.
菜闻起来好香哦  莫妮卡
The food smells great, Mon.
这里布置得真漂亮
And the place looks so nice.
感恩节快乐  各位
Hey, happy Thanksgiving, everybody!
感恩节快乐
Happy Thanksgiving!
-真是开心  -再见
- Well, this has been great. - See you.
你们要去哪里
Where you going?
我们说过要去
We did say we'd stop by
乔伊室友的聚会露个面
this little thing Joey's roommate is having.
辣妹舞者吉宁吗
Oh, Janine, the really hot dancer girl?
有些人会说她很有魅力
Some would say she's attractive, yes.
还有谁会去
Who else is going to be there?
她的几个朋友
Some of her friends.
舞者朋友
Her dancer friends?
对啦  好不好
Yes! All right?
她的性感舞者朋友都会去
All of her hot dancer friends are gonna be there...
她们会喝酒跳舞  我们真的很想去嘛
and they'll be drinking and dancing and we really want to go!
伙计  本来都快成功了
Dude, we were good.
你们哪儿也不准去
You're not gonna go anywhere,
你们说过在这吃饭  谁也别想跑
you said you were gonna eat here, and you're gonna eat here!
扔下我们去看性感舞者
Yeah, and leaving us to go see hot dancer girls...
这种行为太不感恩了
...is not very Thanksgiving- y.
但是
Oh, but-but it is,
第一个感恩节就是这样
lt's like the first Thanksgiving
印地安人和清教徒共进晚餐
when the Indians and the Pilgrims uh, sat down to dinner.
然后印地安人告诉清教徒
Then the lndians taught the Pilgrims...
新世界的性感定义是什么
...what it meant to be hot in the New World!
-大家好  -大家好
- Hello, everybody! - Hi!
爸  妈
Hi, Dad. Mom.
看  快看  是钱德勒哦
Look! Look who it is! lt's Chandler!
是啊  钱德勒  你好
Oh, yes, of course. Hello, Chandler.
伯父伯母  你们的气色真好
Mr. and Mrs. Geller, you look wonderful.
很高兴你们能来  外套给我们吧
lt is great to have you here. Let us take your coats.
外面在下雪吗
Whoa, it snowing out there?
没有
No.
莫妮卡  菜看起来都好好吃
Monica, all this food looks wonderful.
你应该考虑干这一行谋生
You should do this for a living.
就算我有头皮屑
Okay, l have dandruff.
你也不必指着我笑
There's no need to laugh and point.
爸  钱德勒是在笑你的笑话
Dad, Chandler was just laughing at your joke.
我的笑话又不好笑
My joke wasn't funny.
瑞秋  我刚刚想到
Rach, l just remembered.
我昨晚梦到盖勒先生
l had a dream about Mr. Geller last night.
真的吗
Really?
对  我梦到他把我从火场救出
Yeah. l dreamt that he saved me from a burning building...
他好英勇好强壮
...and he was so brave and so strong.
让我对他完全改观
And it's making me look at him totally differently.
他以前只是杰克·盖勒
Y'know, I mean he used to be just, y'know
莫妮卡和罗斯的爸爸
"Jack Geller Monica and Ross's dad"
现在他是杰克·盖勒  我的梦中情人
Now he's "Jack Geller, dream hunk."
不知道
l don't know.
对我来说他永远都是杰克·盖勒
No. You know, to me, he'll always be "Jack Geller...
在你换衣服时闯进来
...walks in while you're changing."
爸  钱德勒是罗斯最要好的朋友之一
You know, Dad, Chandler is one of Ross' very best friends.
罗斯是个好青年
Ross sure is a great guy.
我一直觉得儿子
You know I've always felt that how a young man turns out
就是父亲的翻版
...is a reflection on his father.
我也有深有同感
l always thought that too.
请问你爸是做什么的
Tell me, what does your father do?
他是同志
He's a headliner of a...
歌舞秀的头牌
...gay burlesque show.
瑞秋  急死我们了
Rach, you're killing us here,
能快点上甜点吗
Will you serve the dessert already?
有酒醉的舞者都在等我们
There's drunken dancers a- waiting!
你们看  很漂亮吧
Look at it. lsn't it beautiful?
是啊  这是什么
Yeah. What is it?
酒果酱松糕  有很多层
lt's a trifle. lt's got all these layers.
先是一层松脆饼  然后是一层果酱
First there's a layer of ladyfingers, then a layer of jam,
然后是我自己做的乳蛋糕
...then custard, which l made from scratch...
然后是覆盆子  然后更多松脆饼
...then raspberries, more ladyfingers...
然后是豌豆洋葱炒嫩牛肉
...then beef sauteed with peas and onions...
然后又有一点乳蛋糕
...then a little bit more custard...
然后是香蕉  最后在上面涂上鲜奶油
...then bananas and then l put whipped cream on top.
香蕉前面是什么
What was the one right before bananas?
炒牛肉吗  我也觉得有点奇怪
The beef. Yeah, that was weird to me too.
不过我想说连甜肉馅饼都有了
But then, y'know, I thought "well, there's mincemeat pie,"
那是也是一种英式甜点
I mean that's an English dessert,
英国人会放一堆怪东西在食物里嘛
These people just put strange things in their food.
对了  可以借你家的兰姆酒吗
Oh! By the way, can I borrow some Rum from your place?
当然可以
Yeah, sure.
我不在的时候  你们可别偷吃哦
And while I'm gone don't you boys sneak a taste.
甜点加牛肉
Beef in a dessert?
不 不  不可能好吃
No, no, no. There is no way.
就是啊  而且果酱才一层
l know. And only one layer of jam?
有没有搞错啊
What is up with that?
天哪
Oh, my God.
这两页黏在一起了
The pages are stuck together.
钱德勒
Chandler!
天啊  她做了酒果酱松糕加
Oh, my God. She made half an English trifle and...
肉馅马铃薯泥饼
...half a shepherd's pie!
完了  她得重做了
Man, now she's gonna start all over.
我们不能介绍辣妹认识新世界了
We're never gonna get to introduce the hot girls to the New World.
不  我们可以
No, no, we will.
不要告诉她就是了
We just won't tell her she messed up.
然后让她给大家吃牛肉乳蛋糕吗
Just let her serve the beef-custard thing?
对  这会是个有趣的感恩节回忆
Yeah. lt'll be like a funny Thanksgiving story.
呕吐的回忆的确很有趣
Vomiting stories are funny, l guess.
乔伊  天啊  你家热死了
Joey. God, your apartment is, like, 100 degrees.
你会不会想脱到只剩内衣
Did it make you want to walk around in your underwear?
不会
No.
还不够热
Still not hot enough!
-瑞秋  -怎么了
- Rachel. - Yeah?
你看他
Okay, look at him.
你看那双有力的手
Look at those strong hands.
我真想当那瓶  炼乳
Oh, what l wouldn't give to be that can of condensed milk.
妈  钱德勒说你的毛衣很好看
Mom. Chandler was just saying how beautiful your sweater is.
谢谢你  这是我刚买的新衣服
Oh, thank you Chandler! I just bought it.
是吗  很漂亮
Oh, yes. Well it's very beautiful.
米黄色  又紧身
and it's cream-colored and tight and....
我不是指很紧身  不会很紧啦
l don't mean tight. I mean it's not too tight,
我没有在看...
Not that l was looking at....
他是怎么回事
What's the matter with him?
大概又嗑药了
l think he's stoned again.
-什么  -什么
- What? - What?
伙计  我有事要告诉你
Dude, I need to talk to you a sec.
我大概知道  我爸妈为什么不喜欢你了
Okay, I think I might know why my parents don't like you.
是吗  为什么
You do? Why?
记不记得我们年轻的时候
Okay, remember we were young.
大二的春假
Spring break, sophomore year,
我在房里抽大麻
l got high in my bedroom...
我爸妈走进来闻到了
...and my parents walked in and smelled it...
于是我就说是你刚抽了大麻
...so l told them that you had gotten stoned
然后跳窗跑了
and jumped out the window.
什么  你为什么要赖到我身上
What?! Why did you do that?
我不知道
l don't know.
我第一个想到的  就是你的名字
Yours was the first name that popped into my head.
对不起  我以为不会怎样
I'm I'm sorry. I-I didn't think it would matter.
怎么可能不会怎样呢
How could it not matter?
我怎么知道我们会从室友变成死党
How was I supposed to know we'd end up being friends after college,
更想不到你会跟我妹同居了
...and you'd be living with my sister?
那些"生死之交"的豪言呢
What about the "friends forever" stuff?
不晓得  我当时嗑傻了
l don't know. l was all high.
爸妈叫我来看看
Mom and Dad sent me to find out
你是不是想找罗斯嗑药
if you were trying to get Ross stoned.
罗斯大学抽大麻被他们逮到
Your parents caught Ross smoking pot in college,
他居然赖到我身上
and he blamed it on me!
罗斯  你怎么能这样呢
Ross, I can't believe you'd do that!
就是因为他们讨厌我  我们才没公开
We haven't told them we're together because they hate me, okay?
麻烦你搞定他们
So will you fix this?
好啦  我会说抽嗨的不是钱德勒
Okay, okay, l'll tell them it wasn't Chandler who got high.
那我要说是谁呢
Now, who should l say it was?
你啊  这又没什么
You! lt's not like it's a big deal.
你现在又没在嗑药
You don't still do it or anything.
好啦好啦
All right.
那我要说是谁骗我这么做的呢
Now, who should l say tricked me into doing it?
爸  请别在这里剔牙
Dad, please don't pick your teeth out here.
如果你要翘脚  怎么不坐
And if you're gonna put your feet up- -
莫妮卡  不要烦他
Monica, leave him alone!
你快点好吗
Will you hurry up?
你之前没听到我说
Did you not hear me before when I told you that
吉宁全部朋友都是舞者吗
all of Janine's friends are dancers?!
而且她们会喝很多酒
And that they're gonna be drinking a lot?
我是听到了
No, l did.
不过你再说一次  好浪漫喔
But tell me again because it's so romantic.
你打得好慢  不能快一点吗
Well you're whipping so slow! Can't you do it any faster?
乔伊  拜托  我不想出错
Joey! Come on! I don't wanna make any mistakes, alright?
甜点只有这一道
This is the only dessert
要是我搞砸  大家会说
if l screw it up, everybody's gonna be like:
"记得那次感恩节
"oh, remember that Thanksgiving
瑞秋把酒果酱松糕做坏了吗"
when Rachel screwed up the trifle?"
所以酒果酱松糕留给我去担心
So why don't you just let me worry about making the trifle
你只管担心吃下去的事  可以吗
And you just worry about eating it, alright?
我是很担心
Oh, l am.
罗斯  你再不说  我就要说了
Ross, lf you don't tell them, then l will.
好啦
Okay. Fine.
罗斯  你可以来一下吗
Ross, can l talk to you for a second?
乔伊  等一下  好吗
Oh, uh, can it wait a second Joey?
我有事要告诉我爸妈
l have to tell my parents something.
不能等是吗  好吧
No, it can't? Okay.
我们应该告诉瑞秋  她甜品做砸了
Okay, look, I think we have to tell Rachel she messed up her dessert.
什么  大家是都怎么了
What?! What is with everybody?
今天是感恩节  不是
lt's Thanksgiving, not...
告解日
...Truth Day!
等大家吃到那道香蕉牛肉甜点
Look, when everyone eats that banana-meat thing...
一定会取笑她  你希望这样嘛
...they'll all make fun of her. Do you want that?
好  我们就叫大家
Okay, okay, we'll just get everyone to act
假装好吃就行了
like they like it.
那样就不会有人取笑她
That way, no one makes fun of her...
我们也能去找那些"香甜小土豆甜心"
...and we still get to go to sweet-potato pie.
伙计  别把她们物化
Dude, they're not objects.
开玩笑的  我去告诉大家  你把瑞秋支开
Just kidding. l'll talk to them. You distract her.
瑞秋  可以出去谈一下吗
Hey, Rach, can l talk to you outside for a sec?
好吧
Okay.
什么事  罗斯
What's up, Ross?
所以
So....
感恩节
Thanksgiving.
岁末季节又来了
The holiday season is upon us.
是啊
Yeah.
还有
And...
你今天很漂亮
...you look nice today.
-不  罗斯  别这样  -什么
- Oh, no. No, Ross, don't do this. - What?
我觉得我们不能复合
I just- I don't think us getting back together is a good idea.
我早就料到会这样  罗斯
l thought this might happen today. Ross,
我知道逢年过节特别难熬
l know the holidays can be rough...
而且你一个人肯定很辛苦
you know, and it's probably hard for you to be alone right now.
你也是一个人
You're alone.
不  我跟菲比住
No, l live with Phoebe.
你就真的只有一个人
l mean, you're alone-alone.
但这个时机真的不对  抱歉
And it's just not the time for us. l'm sorry.
没事  我就想试试看
Oh, well. Can't blame a guy for trying.
要是有人不知道怎么装好吃
And if anyone needs help pretending to like it...
我有在表演课学过
...l learned some things in acting class.
你们可以摸摸肚子
Try rubbing your stomach.
或是说"嗯"
Or saying, "Mmm."
还有微笑
And smiling.
好吗
Okay?
我再也不花钱让你去上表演课了
l'm not gonna pay for those acting classes anymore.
瑞秋  你回来了
Rachel, there you are.
拜托  快上甜点吧
Come on, let's serve that dessert already!
乔伊  别再催我了
Joey, you have to stop rushing me.
-你知道吗  罚你不准吃  -真的吗
- You know what? You don't get any dessert. - Really?
假的  骗你的
No, I'm just kidding
我才不会这样对你呢
l would never do that to you.
好  各位  酒果酱松糕时间到
Okay, everybody, it's trifle time.
瑞秋  这是英式酒果酱松糕对吧
So, Rach, this is a traditional English trifle, isn't it?
一点也没错
lt sure is.
那你是加牛肉还是茄子
So did you make it with beef or eggplant?
-牛肉  -我不能吃  你也知道我不吃肉
- Beef. - l can't have any. l don't eat meat.
莫妮卡  我想让你第一个尝尝
Alright, Monica, I want you to have the first taste.
是吗
Really?
等等  你只挖了鲜奶油
Oh oh oh, wait! You only got whipped cream in there!
你得挖到每一层
You gotta take a bite with all the layers.
好咧
OK.
等等  你掉了一颗豌豆
Op! Wait, you dropped a pea.
怎么样
Well?
好好吃
lt's good.
真的吗  有多好吃
Really? How good?
好吃到我一个人吃
lt's so good that l feel selfish...
会觉得过意不去
...about being the only one who's eating it.
我们应该让每个人都享用
l think we should have everyone taste how good it is.
尤其是罗斯
Especially Ross.
真是太好吃了
This is so good
我要去阳台好好品尝
that l'm gonna go enjoy it on the balcony.
好边看风景边享用
So that l can enjoy the view whilst l enjoy my dessert.
我要去莫妮卡房里
I've gotta call my friend Mary
打电话给我朋友玛丽  告诉她有多好吃
...and tell her how good this is from Monica's room.
我帮你拨号
l'll help you dial.
我要去浴室
l'm gonna go into the bathroom...
好边吃边照镜子
...so l can look at it in the mirror as l eat it.
好吧  这是怎么回事
Okay, now what was that all about?
不好吃吗
Does it not taste good?
-我吃吃看  -什么  不行
- Let me try it. - Wha? No no! Ah!
我吃光了
All gone!
好好吃
So good.
也许钱德勒还有剩
Maybe Chandler has some left.
味道像洗脚水
lt tastes like feet.
我喜欢
l like it!
不是吧
Are you kidding?
有什么不好  乳蛋糕  赞
What's not to like? Custard, good.
果酱  赞  牛肉  赞
Jam, good. Meat, good.
所以是被鸟一把抢走
So a bird just grabbed it...
然后叼着飞走
...and then tried to fly away with it...
最后掉到马路上了
...and then just dropped it on the street?
对  不过值得安慰的是
Yes, but if it's any consolation,
掉下去之前  它好像吃得很开心
before the bird dropped it...he seemed to enjoy it.
瑞秋  来一下
Rachel, come here.
我刚刚小睡一觉
l was taking my Thanksgiving nap
结果又梦到杰克
And I had another dream about Jack.
菲比  我会想听吗
Pheobe, Do l want to hear this?
我不知道  你听听看
l don't know, let's see.
我梦到我们正要结婚
So, okay, I dreamt that we were gonna get married,
结果他离开去救火
...and he left because he had to go fight a fire.
所以我去一家夜总会
And, um, so okay, I went to a night club,
却看到他跟一个女的在亲热
and l saw him making out with a girl.
天啊  他在梦里背叛你
Oh, my God, he dream-cheated on you!
对  但这时雅克·库斯托出现
Yeah, but then Jacques Cousteau came...
帮我狠狠地教训了他一顿
...and he kicked his ass for betraying me.
超酷的
So cool!
然后他带我去潜水
Then, he took me diving
跟我介绍他养的海马
and he introduced me to his pet seahorse,
它还一直对我献殷勤
Who, by the way, was totally coming on to me
但我怎么可能给她机会哦
and please, that is not gonna happen.
幸好我今天系了大皮带
Boy, l'm glad l wore the big belt today.
五分钟前  那话会让我神魂颠倒
Five minutes ago, a line like that would have floored me.
现在却毫无作用
But now, nothing.
还是有一点啦  我毕竟是女人嘛
Well, not nothing. l am still a woman.
罗斯  来吧
Ross? Let's go.
对哦  关于告诉爸妈这件事
Oh, yeah. About telling Mom and Dad...
我考虑是否用写信的形式
...l was thinking about maybe writing a letter.
够了  我给过你机会了
Alright, you know what? That's it. You've had your chance.
妈  爸
Mom, Dad.
-罗斯大学的时候抽大麻  -什么
- Ross smoked pot in college. - What?
你个告密者
You are such a tattletale!
妈  爸
Mom, Dad...
记得你们在我房里
...you remember that time you walked in my room...
闻到大麻的事吗
...and smelled marijuana?
记得
Yes.
我说是钱德勒
l told you it was Chandler...
抽的大麻  其实...
...who was smoking the pot but...
是我  对不起
...it was me. l'm sorry.
原来是你
lt was you?
爸  还记得被你害革职的邮差吗
And Dad, you know that mailman that you got fired?
他没有偷你的色情杂志  是罗斯偷的
He didn't steal your Playboys. Ross did.
前廊的秋千椅不是被飓风弄坏的
Yeah, well, Hurricane Gloria didn't break the porch swing, Monica did!
是莫妮卡坐坏的
Monica did!
罗斯已经离职博物馆一年了
Ross hasn't worked at the museum for a year!
莫妮卡和钱德勒在同居
Monica and Chandler are living together!
罗斯在赌城娶了瑞秋  然后又被离婚了
Ross married Rachel in Vegas! And got divorced! Again!
我爱雅克·库斯托
l love Jacques Cousteau!
我不应该在酒果酱松糕里放牛肉
l wasn't supposed to put beef in the trifle!
我想走啦
l want to go!
这三十秒真是高潮不断啊
That's a lot of information to get in 30 seconds.
好  乔伊  你想走就走吧
All right. Joey, if you want to leave, just leave.
瑞秋  这道甜点的确不能放肉
Rachel, no, you weren't supposed to put beef in the trifle.
一点也不好吃
lt did not taste good.
菲比  很抱歉
Phoebe, l'm sorry...
但雅克·库斯托已经死了
...but l think Jacques Cousteau is dead.
莫妮卡  我搞不懂
Monica, why you felt you had to hide the fact...
你为何要隐瞒一段如此重要的感情
...that you're in an important relationship is beyond me.
其实秋千椅的事我们心里有数
And we kind of figured about the porch swing.
罗斯
Ross.
嗑药
Drugs?
三度离婚
Divorced again?
儿子  你是怎么了
What happened, son?
我都是遭人哄骗
l got tricked into all those things.
钱德勒  你一直当罗斯的好朋友
Chandler, you've been Ross' best friend all these years...
在他嗑药时仍不放弃他
...stuck by him during the drug problems...
现在你又照顾起莫妮卡
...and now you've taken on Monica as well.
我不知道该说什么
Well, l don't know what to say.
你真是个大好人
You're a wonderful human being.
-谢谢你  -不
- Thank you! - No.
是谢谢你
Thank you!
莫妮卡  罗斯
Monica and Ross,
我真不知道该拿你们俩怎么办
l don't know what l'm gonna do about the two of you.
我会跟他们谈
l'll talk to them.
各位  那是香蕉
You guys, it was bananas...
奶油加牛肉耶
...cream and beef!
你们居然因为怕我难过而吃掉
l just cannot believe that you ate that so that l wouldn't feel bad.
其实我没吃
Well, actually, l didn't eat mine.
还放在浴室里呢
lt's still in the bathroom.
没了  我吃掉了
No, l ate that.
我们的放在莫妮卡的房里了
And we left ours in Monica's bedroom.
没了  我吃了  你的也是
Nope, got it and got yours too.